{
    "questions":[
        {
            "question":"Who invented JavaScript?",
            "optionA":"Douglas Crockford",
            "optionB":"Sheryl Sandberg",
            "optionC":"Brendan Eich",
            "optionD":"Guido van Rossum",
            "answer":"optionC"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which one of these is a JavaScript package manager?",
            "optionA":"Node.js",
            "optionB":"TypeScript",
            "optionC":"npm",
            "optionD":"React js",
            "answer":"optionC"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which tool can you use to ensure code quality?",
            "optionA":"Angular",
            "optionB":"jQuery",
            "optionC":"RequireJS",
            "optionD":"ESLint",
            "answer":"optionD"
        },
        {
            "question":"JavaScript is a ___ -side programming language.",
            "optionA":"Client",
            "optionB":"Server",
            "optionC":"Both",
            "optionD":"None",
            "answer":"optionC"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following will write the message “Hello DataFlair!” in an alert box?",
            "optionA":"alertBox(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
            "optionB":"alert(Hello DataFlair!);",
            "optionC":"msgAlert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
            "optionD":"alert(“Hello DataFlair!”);",
            "answer":"optionD"
        },
        {
            "question":"How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript?",
            "optionA":"min(x,y);",
            "optionB":"Math.min(x,y)",
            "optionC":"Math.min(xy)",
            "optionD":"min(xy);",
            "answer":"optionB"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which JavaScript label catches all the values, except for the ones specified?",
            "optionA":"catch",
            "optionB":"label",
            "optionC":"try",
            "optionD":"default",
            "answer":"optionD"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which are the correct “if” statements to execute certain code if “x” is equal to 2?",
            "optionA":"if(x 2)",
            "optionB":"if(x = 2)",
            "optionC":"if(x == 2)",
            "optionD":"if(x != 2 )",
            "answer":"optionC"
        },
        {
            "question":"What will the code return? Boolean(3 < 7)",
            "optionA":"true",
            "optionB":"false",
            "optionC":"NaN",
            "optionD":"SyntaxError",
            "answer":"optionA"
        },
        {
            "question":"What will the code return? Boolean(3 < 7)",
            "optionA":"true",
            "optionB":"false",
            "optionC":"NaN",
            "optionD":"SyntaxError",
            "answer":"optionA"
        }
    ]
}